const quiz3data = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "You look hungry, so I ___ you something to eat.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will bring", isCorrect: true},
      {answer: "bring", isCorrect: false},
    ],
    help: 'We use the future simple to express a spontaneous decision. We make the decision spontaneously at the time of speaking (no plan). '
 },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "I ___ more about this topic in my next lecture.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will say", isCorrect: false},
      {answer: "will be saying", isCorrect: true},
    ],
    help: 'We use the future continuous when we talk about an activity or event going on at a particular time or over a particular period in the future.'
 },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Thanks for lending me the money, I ___ you back on Monday.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will pay", isCorrect: true},
      {answer: "pay", isCorrect: false},
    ],
    help: 'We use the future simple when promising to do something.'
 },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "I think I ___ to the new shop tomorrow.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will go", isCorrect: true},
      {answer: "am going to go", isCorrect: false},
    ],
    help: 'We often use the future simple with the verb to think before it.'
 },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "I _____ when you arrive.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will sleep", isCorrect: false},
      {answer: "will be sleeping", isCorrect: true},
    ],
    help: 'We use the future continuous to show a future action in progress during another shorter future action or a specific time.'
 },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Where is your ticket? The bus ___ any minute.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will arrive", isCorrect: true},
      {answer: "arrives", isCorrect: false},
    ],
    help: 'We use the future simple to express a prediction, hope, opinion, or assumption regarding the future.'
 },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: " That bag looks heavy. I ___  you with it.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "help", isCorrect: false},
      {answer: "will help", isCorrect: true},
    ],
    help: "We use the future simple when offering to do something."
 },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "The government ____ a statement about the crisis later today.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will be making", isCorrect: true},
      {answer: "will make", isCorrect: false},
    ],
    help: 'We use the future continuous to talk about complete actions in the future.'
 },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "It's late. I think I ___ to bed now.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will go", isCorrect: true},
      {answer: "go", isCorrect: false},
    ],
    help: 'We use the future simple when we state a decision made at the moment of speaking.'
 },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "She ____ every day until the end of the month.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will perform", isCorrect: false},
      {answer: "will be performing", isCorrect: true},
    ],
    help: 'We use the future continuous when the future activity or event is the result of a previous decision or arrangement.'
 },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "The meeting ___ begin at 9.00 am.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "is going to", isCorrect: false},
      {answer: "will", isCorrect: true},
    ],
    help: 'In a formal style, we use will rather than going to to talk about future events that have been previously arranged in some detail.'
 },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "The team's star player is injured and ___ in the game on Saturday.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "won't be playing", isCorrect: true},
      {answer: "won't play", isCorrect: false},
    ],
    help: "We use the future continuous to talk about complete actions in the future.",
    help1: "will not = won't"
 },
]
export default quiz3data
